gethdporn.com 2017-12-23

# 

* ### Introduction

  1. Sun Media Limited ("Operator") as the operator of metaporn.com respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy ("Policy") explains how the Operator will treat information that it may obtain from you ("User") as you make use of the metaporn.com website and all other services provided by the Operator ("Service"). Please read this Policy carefully. By accessing the metaporn.com website or otherwise using the Service and the websites which are referred or linked to on the Service (each of these websites a "Third Party Service"), you agree to be bound by this Policy. If you do not agree to any provision of this Policy, you are not entitled to access the metaporn.com website and use the Service.
  2. This Policy may be revised from time to time by the Operator without notice to the User other than appearing on the Service. It is the User's responsibility to regularly check the Service and to review the Policy in its current version as published on the Service. The User's continued use of the Service constitutes the User's agreement to all revisions to the Policy. The Policy was last revised on February 6, 2015.

* ### THE SERVICE AND THIRD PARTY SITES

This Policy applies solely to the Service. The Service provides links to sponsor, advertiser, or other third-party websites, including the Third Party Services that are not owned or controlled by the Operator and are not governed by this Policy. The Operator has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, any third-party content including the privacy policies and practices of any third parties. The User agrees that it is responsible for reviewing and understanding the privacy policies (if any) of any third-party websites the User may access through the Service. By accessing or using the Service, the User agrees to release the Operator from any and all liability arising from the User's use of any third-party website, content, service, or software accessed through the Service, including the Third Party Services.

* ### INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THE SERVICE

  1. When the User uses the Service, the Operator may collect and store passive information about the User's visit. Passive information is any form of aggregate data, navigational data, tracking data, click-stream data, or historical data. It may include the domain name of the User's Internet service provider (e.g., whether the User logged on from aol.com or whitehouse.gov), referral data (e.g., the address of the last URL the User visited prior to clicking through to the Service) as well as device, operating system and browser type (e.g., a Firefox browser on an Apple computer running on a Macintosh operating system). The Operator uses this information to track and analyze how users access and use the Service.
  2. In addition, when the User uses the Service the Operator generally collects and stores the IP-address of the device the User is using to access the Service. (An IP, or "Internet Protocol," address is a unique number associated with an Internet device that may be communicated to other computers and servers when the Internet is used.) The Operator uses this information for purposes of security and anti-fraud protection.
  3. The Operator also uses cookies and/or web beacons on the Service. (A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to the Internet browser from a Web server and stored on a computer's hard drive, and that may be accessed when a website or other online service is used. A web beacon is a small, transparent graphic image placed on a website, which allows the site to record the actions of a visitor opening the page that contains the beacon.)
  4. The Operator may use cookies or web beacons to: (1) determine whether users of the Service are unique, or whether the same user is using the Service on multiple occasions; (2) help deliver advertisements; (3) track usage throughout various components of the metaporn.com website and the Service (e.g., tracking where traffic comes from and how users navigate through the Service, etc.); (4) store the User's agreement to the Terms of Service and this Policy; (5) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.
  5. The User may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings in its browser. In that case the full functionality of the Service may not be available.
  6. These information collected by the Operator do not, on their own, personally identify the User. However, they can potentially be combined with information obtained from other sources in to identify the User. The Operator does not ordinarily seek or obtain personally identifying information about users from others. The Operator reserves the right to seek such information in the event of a violation of the Operator's Terms of Service, in the event of a dispute between the Operator and the User, or if required by law to do so.

* ### USE OF VISITOR INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THE SERVICE

The Operator does not share the information collected by the Operator in the ordinary operation of the Service. The Operator may obtain and merge information about users, and usage of the Service into aggregated data, which may then be used by the Operator and/or shared with advertisers or others. When the Operator provides aggregated information to third parties, these third parties will not receive any personally identifiable data and will not be able to identify the User or contact the User based on that data.

* ### USAGE INFORMATION - COLLECTION AND USE BY ADVERTISERS AND OTHERS

  1. The Operator allows third parties to display advertisements using the Service. These third parties use technology on the Service to deliver advertisements for the User to see directly in its browser. In doing so, the third parties may automatically receive the User's IP-address. Other third parties that place advertising using the Service may have the ability to use cookies and/or web beacons to collect information of the User, including information about the User's usage of the Service.
  2. The Operator does not control the processes that advertisers use to collect information of the User. However, IP-addresses, cookies and web beacons alone generally cannot be used to identify individuals, only machines. Therefore, advertisers and others whose advertisements or content may be provided through the Service generally will not know who the User is unless additional information is provided to them by a response by the User to an advertisement, by entering into an agreement with them, or by other means.

* ### CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

The Operator does not knowingly allow children to use the Service, and all users of the Service must confirm that they are at least 21 years of age. The Operator does not collect or maintain information from those users the Operator actually knows are under the age of 21, and no part of the Service is designed to attract anyone under 21. If the Operator becomes aware that anyone under the age of 21 is using the Service, their access to the Service will be terminated.

* ### PERMITTED DISCLOSURES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

The Operator will not disclose any personally identifiable information it obtains except: (1) as described in the Operator's Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy; (2) after obtaining the User's permission to a specific use or disclosure; (3) as required to protect the Operator's property, safety, or operations, or the property or safety of others; (4) if the Operator is required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process or governmental request (such as a court order, search warrant, subpoena, civil discovery request, or statutory requirement); or (5) as otherwise required by law.

* ### CONTACTING THE OPERATOR

For any questions or concerns about this Policy or the use of personal information, please contact the Operator via [support@metaporn.com.](mailto:support@metaporn.com)
